welovemacs.com 2009-06-28

# Privacy Statement, Apple Mac and iPod Accessories

## Privacy Statement

We, at **"We Love Macs"!** have designed our business practices to safeguard your privacy and be responsible for use of your personal information. In fact, protecting your privacy is the foundation of our "Customer For Life" commitment. 

In order to assist you with your on-line purchases, on our secured website [ http://www.welovemacs.com](http://www.welovemacs.com/) there will be times when we will need personal information from you, such as your name, home address, e-mail address or telephone number by which to reach you to confirm the information you have supplied us. 

**"We Love Macs"!** will seek at all times to appropriately protect the information you give to us by using security technology for all credit card data. 

Some of the information **"We Love Macs"!** receives about you or your session may be used for research and to help us to improve the site and the services we offer to our customers. In general the Internet addresses of computers, also known as IP addresses, are logged to track user sessions while they remain anonymous. We analyze this data for certain trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. 

**"We Love Macs"!** does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. 

If you have any questions about the privacy statement of **"We Love Macs"!** , please feel free to email us your questions or concerns at [info@welovemacs.com](mailto:info@welovemacs.com). 

**Third-Party Web Beacons:** We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com).
